Stjepan Grgić

Digital Product Designer

grgic.stjepan@gmail.com | +44 7732 877 679 | Moving to London stjepangrgic.com | linkedin.com/in/stjepangrgic

Summary -

Analytical and creative designer with over six years of experience in both startups and advertising agencies looking to join a challenging position with the ability to have ownership, responsibility and grow as a professional and as a person.

Work Experience -

Sabbatical / Travel break | January 2019 - September 2019

OptimoRoute | optimoroute.com

Lead UI/UX Designer | July 2017 - January 2019 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Worked on improving the experience of existing tools to enable businesses to run planing and delivery optimisations more efficiently.
- Involved in creating and designing the user experience and interface of new product features (Real-time Order Tracking, Customer notifications, Delivery breadcrumbs) from the ground up.
- Lead design projects (landing pages, marketing campaigns, presentations, sales collateral) for the OptimoRoute marketing and sales team

Axilis | axilis.com

Lead UI/UX Designer | March 2017 - July 2017 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Lead design of a healthcare SaaS product for the US based client. That included design and experience of Android based tablet and phone applications as well as an admin web application.
- Designed company website.

Underlayer

Founder & Digital Product Designer | December 2015 - July 2017 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Personal design studio.
- Lead user experience and user interfaces design for multiple projects, some of which are:
 - Agrivi | stjepangrgic.com/work/agrivi (case study)
 - Memgraph | memgraph.com
 - HCV Dnevnik (iOS App) | App store link
 - TalkBook | talkbook.co

Vibby | <u>vibby.com</u> | <u>stjepangrgic.com/work/vibby</u> (case study) **Product Designer** | March 2015 - January 2016 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Responsible for designing user experience and interface of every aspect of the product video player, 'vib' creation process, profiles, dashboard, explore page...
- Created countless wireframes and interactive prototypes.
- Involved in frontend development and 'sliced' online player, as well as the majority of other features of the web application.
- Designed new branding, presentations for investors, business cards, shirts ...

Summary of skills

- Advanced skills using design tools such as:
 Sketch, Photoshop, Ilustrator, Figma
- Prototyping and UX tools:
 InVision, OmniGraffle, Axure
- Proficient with 'slicing' designs using HTML and CSS
- Confident with: JavaScript (Vue.js, Gatsby.js), Git, Terminal After Effects Animation
- Other:
 Sketching, Drawing, Photography

Personal Skills

- Critical thinker
- Problem solver
- Good Listener
- Open-Minded
- Ability to adapt to multicultural environments
- Attention to details

Languages

- Croatian Native proficiency
- English Professional working proficiency
- German Elementary proficiency

Hobbies / In free time

- Reading as much as possible
- Photography
- Drawing and Painting

Grey Zagreb | grey.com/croatia

Digital Designer | July 2014 - March 2015 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Worked on a wide range of advertising campaigns for clients like A1 Telekom Austria Group, Microsoft Mobile, Erste Bank Croatia and Croatian National Tourist Board
- Featured projects:
 - Share Istria | Istrian Tourist Board | stjepangrgic.com/work/share-istria (case study)
 - Vip Xmas Chat | A1 Telekom | stjepangrgic.com/work/vip-xmass-chat (case study)

$\textbf{Virtus dizajn} \mid \underline{\text{virtus-dizajn.com}}$

Junior Web Designer & Developer | September 2013 - April 2014 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Designed websites for various local small business.
- Converted designs to HTML and CSS pages.
 - www.alati.info
 - www.liderizalidere.eu/hr/
 - www.bazeni-jerkic.com
 - www.klimaexpert.hr

Točka | tocka.co

Junior designer | September 2013 – April 2014 | Požega, Croatia

- Assisted the team in various design projects.
- Designed a technical manual book for C-DESIGN Fashion software for a local textile design school.

□ -1 + :		
Education		
Luucation		

University of Zagreb, Faculty of Graphic Arts

Bachelor of Arts - BA (Dropout) | grf.unizg.hr/en/ | 2010 - 2013 | Zagreb, Croatia

Other training / online courses	
---------------------------------	--

Coursera

- Gamification, University of Pennsylvania
- Introduction to Psychology, University of Toronto
- Interaction Design Specialization, University of California San Diego

Other

I have gone through many courses from Lynda.com, SkillShare, TutsPlus, DigitalTutors ...